Guide to the Othniel Charles Marsh Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- General correspondence, 1814-1903; Series I
  - Harrington, Bernard James (1848-?), 1875; cuid602 (Box 14, Folder 594)
  - Harris, Gilbert Dennison (1864-?), 1891; cuid603 (Box 14, Folder 595)
  - Harrison, Samuel Alexander (1822-1890), 1868; cuid604 (Box 14, Folder 596)
  - Hartley, Edward, 1870; cuid605 (Box 14, Folder 597)
  - Hartt, Charles Fred (1840-1878), 1860-1868; cuid606 (Box 14, Folder 598)
  - Hartt, Charles Fred (1840-1878), 1869-1873; cuid607 (Box 14, Folder 599)
  - Hartt, Charles Fred (1840-1878), 1874-1876; cuid608 (Box 14, Folder 600)
  - Hastings, Charles Seldon (1848-1932), 1894; cuid609 (Box 14, Folder 601)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1884 June - December; cuid610 (Box 15, Folder 602)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1885 January - April; cuid611 (Box 15, Folder 603)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1885 May - September; cuid612 (Box 15, Folder 604)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1886 March - May; cuid613 (Box 15, Folder 605)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1886 June - October; cuid614 (Box 15, Folder 606)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1887 March - May; cuid615 (Box 15, Folder 607)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1887 June - October; cuid616 (Box 15, Folder 608)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1887 November - December; cuid617 (Box 15, Folder 609)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1888 January - May; cuid618 (Box 15, Folder 610)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1888 June - December; cuid619 (Box 15, Folder 611)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1889 January - April; cuid620 (Box 15, Folder 612)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1889 May - July; cuid621 (Box 15, Folder 613)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1889 August - December; cuid622 (Box 15, Folder 614)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1890 January - April; cuid623 (Box 15, Folder 615)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1890 May - June; cuid624 (Box 15, Folder 616)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1890 July; cuid625 (Box 15, Folder 617)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1890 August - September; cuid626 (Box 15, Folder 618)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1890 October - December; cuid627 (Box 15, Folder 619)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1891 January - March; cuid628 (Box 16, Folder 620)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1891 April - May; cuid629 (Box 16, Folder 621)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1891 June - July; cuid630 (Box 16, Folder 622)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1891 August - September; cuid631 (Box 16, Folder 623)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1891 October - December; cuid632 (Box 16, Folder 624)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1892 January - March; cuid633 (Box 16, Folder 625)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1892 April - June; cuid634 (Box 16, Folder 626)
  - Hatcher, John Bell (1861-1904), 1892 July - 1893 January; cuid635 (Box 16, Folder 627)
  - Haughton, Samuel (1821-1897), 1880; cuid636 (Box 16, Folder 628)
  - Hawkins, Benjamin Waterhouse (1807-1889), 1870; cuid637 (Box 16, Folder 629)
  - Hawley, Joseph Roswell (1826-1905), 1883-1873; cuid638 (Box 16, Folder 630)
  - Hawley, R.E., 1869-1873; cuid639 (Box 16, Folder 631)
  - Hay, John (1838-1905), 1882-1897; cuid640 (Box 16, Folder 632)
  - Hay, Kate Erroll, 1876; cuid641 (Box 16, Folder 633)
  - Hay, Oliver Perry (1846-1930), 1871-1885; cuid642 (Box 16, Folder 634)
  - Hay, Robert (1835-1895), 1883; cuid643 (Box 16, Folder 635)
  - Hay, Mrs. Robert, 1883; cuid644 (Box 16, Folder 636)
  - Hayden, Ferdinand Vandever (1829-1887), 1867-1883; cuid645 (Box 16, Folder 637)
  - Heath, William M., 1871; cuid646 (Box 16, Folder 638)
  - Hebard, Grace Raymond (1861-1936), 1898; cuid647 (Box 16, Folder 639)
  - Hector, James (1834-1907), 1872-1874; cuid648 (Box 16, Folder 640)
  - Heiney, W.M., 1893; cuid649 (Box 16, Folder 641)
  - Heisey, Jacob, 1875; cuid650 (Box 16, Folder 642)
  - Heldreich, T., 1871; cuid651 (Box 16, Folder 643)
  - Hemenway, Mrs. Samuel, 1866-1867; cuid652 (Box 16, Folder 644)
  - Hendrick, G. Dix, undated; cuid653 (Box 16, Folder 645)
  - Henry, Joseph (1797-1878), 1867-1875; cuid654 (Box 16, Folder 646)
  - Henry, Michael, 1886; cuid655 (Box 16, Folder 647)
  - Herbert, Hilary Abner (1834-1919), 1886; cuid656 (Box 16, Folder 648)
  - Herbert, John G., 1869; cuid657 (Box 16, Folder 649)
  - Herbert, O.C., 1869; cuid658 (Box 16, Folder 650)
  - Hermann, Adam, 1876-1892; cuid659 (Box 17, Folder 651)
  - Herring's Express Company, 1874; cuid660 (Box 17, Folder 652)
  - Hersey, Samuel J., 1876; cuid661 (Box 17, Folder 653)
  - Herzer, H., 1876; cuid662 (Box 17, Folder 654)
  - Heukel m, Sigenbeck van, undated; cuid663 (Box 17, Folder 654A)
  - Hewitt, Abram Stevens (1822-1903), 1884-1886; cuid664 (Box 17, Folder 655)
  - Hielscher, Theo., 1883; cuid665 (Box 17, Folder 656)
  - Hiestand, W. D., 1892; cuid666 (Box 17, Folder 657)
  - Hilgard, Eugene Woldmar (1833-1916), 1868-1893; cuid667 (Box 17, Folder 658)
  - Hilgard, Julius Erasmus (1825-1891), 1874-1887; cuid668 (Box 17, Folder 659)
  - Hill, Alfred James (1833-1895), 1868; cuid669 (Box 17, Folder 660)
  - Hill, James Jerome (1838-1916), 1892; cuid670 (Box 17, Folder 661)
  - Hill, Robert Thomas (1858-1941), 1896; cuid671 (Box 17, Folder 662)
  - Hills, Richard Charles (1848-1923), 1889-1897; cuid672 (Box 17, Folder 663)
  - Hinds, John Tredelle Dillard (1847-1921), 1879; cuid673 (Box 17, Folder 664)
  - Hine, William and Co., 1878; cuid674 (Box 17, Folder 665)
  - Hinkle, Philip, 1899; cuid675 (Box 17, Folder 666)
  - Hitchcock, Charles Henry (1836-1919), 1868-1876; cuid676 (Box 17, Folder 667)
  - Hitchcock, Edward, Sr. (1793-1864), 1859; cuid677 (Box 17, Folder 668)
  - Hitchcock, Edward, Jr. (1828-1911), 1867-1892; cuid678 (Box 17, Folder 669)
  - Hodges, Henry Clay (1831-1917), 1886; cuid679 (Box 17, Folder 670)
  - Holbrook, John Edwards (1794-1871), [1862]; cuid680 (Box 17, Folder 671)
  - Holden, Edward Singleton (1846-1914), 1885; cuid681 (Box 17, Folder 672)
  - Holmes, Francis Simmons (1815-1882), [1868]-1869; cuid682 (Box 17, Folder 673)
  - Holmes, Oliver Wendell (1841-1935), 1882-1883; cuid683 (Box 17, Folder 674)
  - Holmes, William Henry (1846-1917), 1885-1889; cuid684 (Box 17, Folder 675)
  - Home, Joseph, 1861; cuid685 (Box 17, Folder 676)
  - Honeyman, David, 1870; cuid686 (Box 17, Folder 677)
  - Hooker, Sir Joseph Dalton (1817-1911), 1878-1885; cuid687 (Box 17, Folder 678)
  - Hopson and Sherman, 1882; cuid688 (Box 17, Folder 679)
  - Horus, Henry, 1867; cuid689 (Box 17, Folder 680)
  - Hoskins, J.C.C., undated; cuid690 (Box 17, Folder 681)
  - Hotchkiss, A.B., 1886; cuid691 (Box 17, Folder 682)
  - Hovey, Edrnund Otis (1862-1924), 1888; cuid692 (Box 17, Folder 683)
  - Hovey, Horace Carter (1833-1914), 1869; cuid693 (Box 17, Folder 684)
  - Howell, Edwin Eugene (1845-1911), 1867-1891; cuid694 (Box 17, Folder 685)
  - Howell, Robert (1801-?), 1869; cuid695 (Box 17, Folder 686)
  - Howland, H.H., 1876; cuid696 (Box 17, Folder 687)
  - Hoyt, Henry Martin (1830-1892), 1885; cuid697 (Box 17, Folder 688)
  - Hoyt, M. L., 1871; cuid698 (Box 17, Folder 689)
  - Hubbard, Elbert Hamilton (1849-3912), 1873; cuid699 (Box 17, Folder 690)
  - Hubbell, S.F., 1878; cuid700 (Box 17, Folder 691)
  - Hubrecht, A. W. (1853-1915), 1896; cuid701 (Box 17, Folder 692)
  - Hudson, Susan E. Johnson, 1866; cuid702 (Box 17, Folder 693)
  - Huffnagle, Alfred, 1875; cuid703 (Box 17, Folder 694)
  - Hughes, McKenny, 1891-1899; cuid704 (Box 17, Folder 695)
  - Hughes, Walter Henry (1858-?), 1874; cuid705 (Box 17, Folder 696)
  - Hulke, John Whitaker (1830-1895), 1873-1892; cuid706 (Box 17, Folder 697)
  - Humboldt, Alexander Freiherr von (1769-1859), 1814; cuid707 (Box 17, Folder 698)
  - Humphrey, Charles Frederic (1844-1926), 1885-1887; cuid708 (Box 17, Folder 699)
  - Humphrey and Co., 1877; cuid709 (Box 17, Folder 700)
  - Humphreys, Andrew Atkinson (1810-1883), 1878; cuid710 (Box 17, Folder 701)
  - Hunt, Thomas Sterry (1826-1892), 1880-1888; cuid711 (Box 17, Folder 702)
  - Huntington, Collis Potter, 1882; cuid712 (Box 17, Folder 703)
  - Hurd, A., 1870-1871; cuid713 (Box 17, Folder 704)
  - Hurd, Mrs. S.H., 1874; cuid714 (Box 17, Folder 705)
  - Hutchinson, Henry Neville (1856-?), 1894; cuid715 (Box 18, Folder 706)
  - Huxley, Henrietta A.H. (?-1915) (Mrs. T.H. Huxley), 1881-1895; cuid716 (Box 18, Folder 707)
  - Huxley, Leonard (1860-1933), 1889-1896; cuid717 (Box 18, Folder 708)
  - Huxley, Thomas Henry (1825-1895), 1876-1885; cuid718 (Box 18, Folder 709)
  - Hyatt, Alpheus (1838-1902), 1868-1896; cuid719 (Box 18, Folder 710)
  - Hyde, D.C., 1880; cuid720 (Box 18, Folder 711)
  - Jackson and Co., 1872; cuid721 (Box 18, Folder 712)
  - Jackson, Charles Loring (1847-1935), 1894; cuid722 (Box 18, Folder 713)
  - Jackson, E., 1867; cuid723 (Box 18, Folder 714)
  - Jackson, George Anson (1846-1907), 1868; cuid724 (Box 18, Folder 715)
  - Jackson, WilliamHicks (1835-1903), 1871; cuid725 (Box 18, Folder 716)
  - Jackson, Mrs. William H., 1871; cuid726 (Box 18, Folder 716A)
  - Jaeger, L.I.F., 1889; cuid727 (Box 18, Folder 717)
  - James, George Wharton (1858-1923), 1898; cuid728 (Box 18, Folder 718)
  - James, T. S, 1894; cuid729 (Box 18, Folder 719)
  - Janeway, John H., 1873-1874; cuid730 (Box 18, Folder 720)
  - Jenks, John Whipple Patter (1819-l894), 1877-1880; cuid731 (Box 18, Folder 721)
  - Jenney, Walter Proctor (1849-?), 1880; cuid732 (Box 18, Folder 722)
  - Jewell, Marshall (1825-1883), 1876; cuid733 (Box 18, Folder 723)
  - Jewett, Ezekiel, 1864-1875; cuid734 (Box 18, Folder 724)
  - Jillson, Res. S., 1871; cuid735 (Box 18, Folder 725)
  - A. J. Johnson Comnany, 1894; cuid736 (Box 18, Folder 726)
  - Johnson, E.J., 1886; cuid737 (Box 18, Folder 727)
  - Johnson, J. Henry, 1873; cuid738 (Box 18, Folder 728)
  - Johnson, Reuben J., 1867; cuid739 (Box 18, Folder 729)
  - Johnson, Reverdy, Jr., 1866; cuid740 (Box 18, Folder 730)
  - Johnson, William Woolsey (1841-1927), 1868; cuid741 (Box 18, Folder 731)
  - Johnston, Christopher (1856-1914), 1888; cuid742 (Box 18, Folder 732)
  - Jones, Charles Colcock (1831-1893), 1877; cuid743 (Box 18, Folder 733)
  - Jones, Charles L., 1880; cuid744 (Box 18, Folder 734)
  - Jones, George M., 1874-1877; cuid745 (Box 18, Folder 735)
  - Jones, John Peter (1847-1916), 1874-1877; cuid746 (Box 18, Folder 736)
  - Jones, Leif, 1890; cuid747 (Box 18, Folder 737)
  - Jones, V.R., 1864-1899; cuid748 (Box 18, Folder 738)
  - Jones, William Albert (1841-1914), 1872-1874; cuid749 (Box 18, Folder 739)
  - Joslyn, W.L., 1882; cuid750 (Box 18, Folder 740)
  - Jost, Henry, 1876; cuid751 (Box 18, Folder 741)
  - Judd, Ada R., 1898; cuid752 (Box 18, Folder 742)
  - Judd, John Wesley (1840-1916), 1895; cuid753 (Box 18, Folder 743)
  - Judd and Detweiler, 1884; cuid754 (Box 18, Folder 744)
  - Judson, John N., 1885; cuid755 (Box 18, Folder 745)
  - Kaldenberg, Frederick Robert (1855-1923), 1898; cuid756 (Box 18, Folder 746)
  - Kalston, J. Grier, 1871; cuid757 (Box 18, Folder 747)
  - Kappeler, Tobias, 1874-1883; cuid758 (Box 18, Folder 748)
  - Kappeler, Tobias, 1884-1895; cuid759 (Box 18, Folder 749)
  - Karpinsky, ___________, 1899; cuid760 (Box 18, Folder 749A)
  - Kearn, Thomas V., 1890; cuid761 (Box 18, Folder 750)
  - Keasbey, George Macculloch (1850-1924), 1873; cuid762 (Box 18, Folder 751)
  - Keep, Robert Porter (1844-1904), 1870-1871; cuid763 (Box 18, Folder 752)
  - Kellogg, George M., 1867; cuid764 (Box 18, Folder 753)
  - Kellogg and Ives, 1868; cuid765 (Box 18, Folder 754)
  - Kellum, Adison B., 1885-1888; cuid766 (Box 18, Folder 755)
  - Kennedy, E., 1880-1883 June; cuid767 (Box 19, Folder 756)
  - Kennedy, E., 1883 July - December; cuid768 (Box 19, Folder 757)
  - Kennedy, E., 1884 January - June; cuid769 (Box 19, Folder 758)
  - Kennedy, E., 1884 July - December; cuid770 (Box 19, Folder 759)
  - Kennedy, E., 1885, undated; cuid771 (Box 19, Folder 760)
  - Kenney, John L., 1882-1883 June; cuid772 (Box 19, Folder 761)
  - Kenney, John L., 1883 July - October; cuid773 (Box 19, Folder 762)
  - Kenney, John L., 1883 November - 1894 May; cuid774 (Box 19, Folder 763)
  - Kent, R.A., 1875; cuid775 (Box 19, Folder 764)
  - Kenton, Richard, 1875; cuid776 (Box 19, Folder 765)
  - Kerr, Washington Caruthers (1827-1885), 1868-1875; cuid777 (Box 19, Folder 766)
  - Kessler, Henry C., 1885-1893; cuid778 (Box 19, Folder 767)
  - Keyes, Charles Rollin (1864-?), 1887; cuid779 (Box 19, Folder 768)
  - Kirnball, James Putnam (1836-1913), 1874; cuid780 (Box 19, Folder 769)
  - Kimball, W.H., 1893; cuid781 (Box 19, Folder 770)
  - Kimball, W.S., 1869; cuid782 (Box 19, Folder 771)
  - King, A.M., 1871; cuid783 (Box 19, Folder 772)
  - King, Clarence (1842-1901), 1876-1887; cuid784 (Box 19, Folder 773)
  - King, Moses (1853-1909), 1883; cuid785 (Box 19, Folder 774)
  - Kingman, W.F., 1898; cuid786 (Box 19, Folder 775)
  - Kinne, O.B., 1867-1881; cuid787 (Box 19, Folder 776)
  - Kinne, William, 1868; cuid788 (Box 19, Folder 777)
  - Kinney, Abbot (1850-1920), 1874; cuid789 (Box 19, Folder 778)
  - Kinney, Ernest L., 1875; cuid790 (Box 19, Folder 779)
  - Kip, Leonard (1826-1906), 1893; cuid791 (Box 19, Folder 780)
  - Kirk, Thomas (1828-1898), 1872; cuid792 (Box 19, Folder 781)
  - Klein, John W., 1876; cuid793 (Box 19, Folder 782)
  - Kline, A.C., 1869; cuid794 (Box 19, Folder 783)
  - Klipstein, D., 1884; cuid795 (Box 19, Folder 784)
  - Kluitz, A. Provo, 1872-1874; cuid796 (Box 19, Folder 785)
  - Knight, John George David (1846-1919), 1890-1891; cuid797 (Box 19, Folder 786)
  - Knight, Wilbur Clinton (1858-1903), 1898; cuid798 (Box 19, Folder 787)
  - Koenen, A. von, 1866; cuid799 (Box 19, Folder 788)
  - Korn, D.H., 1876; cuid800 (Box 19, Folder 789)
  - Kost, John (1819-1904), 1891-1897; cuid801 (Box 19, Folder 790)
  - Kowalevsky, W., 1875-1881; cuid802 (Box 19, Folder 791)
  - Krefft, Gerard, 1872-1875; cuid803 (Box 19, Folder 792)
  - Kruper, Th., 1873; cuid804 (Box 19, Folder 793)
  - Kuki, Jusanami R., 1887; cuid805 (Box 19, Folder 794)
  - Kunz, George Frederick (1856-1932), 1887-1889; cuid806 (Box 19, Folder 795)
  - Lacoe, R.D., 1885; cuid807 (Box 20, Folder 796)
  - Laflarnn, J.A.K., 1883; cuid808 (Box 20, Folder 797)
  - Laidley, William, 1872; cuid809 (Box 20, Folder 798)
  - Lakes, Arthur (1844-?), 1876-1877 June; cuid810 (Box 20, Folder 799)
  - Lakes, Arthur (1844-?), 1877 July - December; cuid811 (Box 20, Folder 800)
  - Lakes, Arthur (1844-?), 1878; cuid812 (Box 20, Folder 801)
  - Lakes, Arthur (1844-?), 1879 March - June; cuid813 (Box 20, Folder 802)
  - Lakes, Arthur (1844-?), 1879 July; cuid814 (Box 20, Folder 803)
  - Lakes, Arthur (1844-?), 1879 August; cuid815 (Box 20, Folder 804)
  - Lakes, Arthur (1844-?), 1879 September; cuid816 (Box 20, Folder 805)
  - Lakes, Arthur (1844-?), 1879 October - November 15; cuid817 (Box 20, Folder 806)
  - Lakes, Arthur (1844-?), 1879 November 16 - December; cuid818 (Box 20, Folder 807)
  - Lakes, Arthur (1844-?), 1880 January; cuid819 (Box 20, Folder 808)
  - Lakes, Arthur (1844-?), 1880 February - April; cuid820 (Box 20, Folder 809)
  - Lakes, Arthur (1844-?), 1888-1895; cuid821 (Box 20, Folder 810)
  - Lambuth, J.W., 1889-1896; cuid822 (Box 20, Folder 811)
  - Lamont, Daniel Scott (1851-1905), 1885; cuid823 (Box 20, Folder 812)
  - Lamothe, L., 1873-1888; cuid824 (Box 20, Folder 813)
  - LaMotte, R.S., 1871; cuid825 (Box 20, Folder 814)
  - Lamson, John S. and Brothers, 1878-1880; cuid826 (Box 20, Folder 815)
  - Landon, H.G., 1871; cuid827 (Box 20, Folder 816)
  - Lane, Edward S., 1871-1873; cuid828 (Box 20, Folder 817)
  - Langley, Samuel Pierrepont (1834-1906), 1884-1896; cuid829 (Box 20, Folder 818)
  - Lankester, Edwin Ray (1847-1929), 1887-1899; cuid830 (Box 20, Folder 819)
  - Lapham, Increase Allen (1811-1875), 1868; cuid831 (Box 20, Folder 820)
  - Lapparent, Albert de, 1899; cuid832 (Box 20, Folder 820A)
  - Lartet, Edouard A.I.H. (1801-1871), 1869; cuid833 (Box 20, Folder 821)
  - Lawrence, C.P., 1884; cuid834 (Box 20, Folder 822)
  - Lawrence, Eugene (1823-1894), 1878; cuid835 (Box 20, Folder 823)
  - Lawson, Andrew Cowper (1861-?), 1894-1895; cuid836 (Box 20, Folder 824)
  - Lea, Isaac (1792-1886), 1868-1885; cuid837 (Box 21, Folder 825)
  - Lea, Mary, 1892; cuid838 (Box 21, Folder 826)
  - Lebourveau, Oscar H., 1874-1876; cuid839 (Box 21, Folder 827)
  - Lebourveau, Oscar H., 1877-1888; cuid840 (Box 21, Folder 828)
  - LeConte, John Lawrence (1825-1883), 1877-1888; cuid841 (Box 21, Folder 829)
  - LeConte, Joseph (1823-1901), 1877-1895; cuid842 (Box 21, Folder 830)
  - Lee, Alfred Emory (1838-?), 1890; cuid843 (Box 21, Folder 831)
  - Leeas, Alfred, 1888; cuid844 (Box 21, Folder 832)
  - Leidy, Joseph (1823-1891), 1867-1890; cuid845 (Box 21, Folder 833)
  - Leiser, A.P., 1887; cuid846 (Box 21, Folder 834)
  - Lemoine, John Emile (1815-1892), 1881; cuid847 (Box 21, Folder 835)
  - Leonard, A.M., 1868; cuid848 (Box 21, Folder 836)
  - LePlongeon, Augustus (1826-1908), 1884-1887; cuid849 (Box 21, Folder 837)
  - Lesquereaux, Leo (1806-1889), 1873-1884; cuid850 (Box 21, Folder 838)
  - Leverett, Frank (1859-?), 1895; cuid851 (Box 21, Folder 839)
  - Leverson, Montague Richard (1830-?), 1886; cuid852 (Box 21, Folder 840)
  - Lighton, W. R, 1886; cuid853 (Box 21, Folder 841)
  - Linsly, Janet, 1877; cuid854 (Box 21, Folder 842)
  - Litton, Abram (1814-1901), 1869-1871; cuid855 (Box 21, Folder 843)
  - Livengood, G.W., 1890; cuid856 (Box 21, Folder 844)
  - Lloyd, John D., 1876; cuid857 (Box 21, Folder 845)
  - Lockwood, Samuel, 1869-1887; cuid858 (Box 21, Folder 846)
  - Lommel, J., 1866; cuid859 (Box 21, Folder 847)
  - Longworth, W.N., 1867-1869; cuid860 (Box 21, Folder 848)
  - Loomis, Elias (1811-1889), 1869; cuid861 (Box 21, Folder 849)
  - Loper, S.W., 1870-1872; cuid862 (Box 21, Folder 850)
    (letter of 5-25-1870. not filmed)
  - Loring, George Bailey (1817-1891), 1882; cuid863 (Box 21, Folder 851)
  - Love, J.G., 1877; cuid864 (Box 21, Folder 852)
  - Lovers, Ivan, 1884; cuid865 (Box 21, Folder 853)
  - Low, Seth (1850-1916), 1891; cuid866 (Box 21, Folder 854)
  - Lowell, James Russell (1819-1891), 1882; cuid867 (Box 21, Folder 855)
  - Lowry, Robert (1830-1910), 1884; cuid868 (Box 21, Folder 856)
  - Lubert, John, 1881-1885; cuid869 (Box 21, Folder 857)
  - Lucas, Frederic Augustus (1852-1929), 1872-1891; cuid870 (Box 21, Folder 858)
  - Lucas, Frederic Augustus (1852-1929), 1892-1900; cuid871 (Box 21, Folder 859)
  - Lucas, O.W., 1879; cuid872 (Box 21, Folder 860)
  - Lumholtz, Carl (1851-1922), 1890; cuid873 (Box 21, Folder 861)
  - Lusk, Frank Stillman (1857-1930), 1894; cuid874 (Box 21, Folder 862)
  - Lydekker, Richard (1849-1915), 1877; cuid875 (Box 21, Folder 863)
  - Lyell, Charles (1797-1875), 1872; cuid876 (Box 21, Folder 864)
  - Lyman, Benjamin Smith (1835-1920), 1868-1898; cuid877 (Box 21, Folder 865)
  - Lyman, Joseph Bardwell (1829-1872), 1869; cuid878 (Box 21, Folder 866)
  - Lyman, Theodore (1833-1897), 1884-1886; cuid879 (Box 21, Folder 867)
  - Lynch, John Arthur (1825-1892), 1890; cuid880 (Box 21, Folder 868)
  - Lyon, Sidney S., 1868; cuid881 (Box 21, Folder 869)
  - Lyons, H.P., 1899; cuid882 (Box 21, Folder 869A)
  - Maartz, G.A., 1873; cuid883 (Box 22, Folder 870)
  - McAdams, William, 1888-1890; cuid884 (Box 22, Folder 871)
  - MacBride, Thomas Huston (1848-1934), 1893-1897; cuid885 (Box 22, Folder 872)
  - McCarthy, H.M., undated; cuid886 (Box 22, Folder 873)
  - McCauley, C.A.H., 1888-1890; cuid887 (Box 22, Folder 874)
  - McChesney, J. D., 1881-1883; cuid888 (Box 22, Folder 875)
  - McChesney, J. D., 1884-1886 June; cuid889 (Box 22, Folder 876)
  - McChesney, J. D., 1886 July - 1896; cuid890 (Box 22, Folder 877)
  - McCrary, George Washington (1835-1890), 1878; cuid891 (Box 22, Folder 878)
  - McDaniel, Z., 1868; cuid892 (Box 22, Folder 879)
  - McDowell, Charles W., 1872-1873; cuid893 (Box 22, Folder 880)
  - McEntee, Jervis (1828-1891), undated; cuid894 (Box 22, Folder 881)
  - McFarland, N.C., 1884; cuid895 (Box 22, Folder 882)
  - McFarland, R.W., 1875; cuid896 (Box 22, Folder 883)
  - McGee, W.J. (1853-1925), 1885-1890; cuid897 (Box 22, Folder 884)
  - McGuin, George B., 1887; cuid898 (Box 22, Folder 885)
  - McLinn, Charles, 1874; cuid899 (Box 22, Folder 886)
  - McLoyd, Charles, 1889; cuid900 (Box 22, Folder 887)
  - MacNaughton, James, 1885-1886; cuid901 (Box 22, Folder 888)
  - McNiel, John A. (1854-1896), 1869-1878; cuid902 (Box 22, Folder 889)
  - McQuitlin, D.A., 1870; cuid903 (Box 22, Folder 890)
  - Madden, D., 1874; cuid904 (Box 22, Folder 891)
  - Maguire, Franck Z., 1885; cuid905 (Box 22, Folder 892)
  - Magur, Charles, 1880; cuid906 (Box 22, Folder 893)
  - Major, C.J. Forsyth, 1886; cuid907 (Box 22, Folder 894)
  - Malcolmson, James W., 1898; cuid908 (Box 22, Folder 895)
  - Mann, Edgar W., 1884; cuid909 (Box 22, Folder 896)
  - Mann, Horace, 1854; cuid910 (Box 22, Folder 896A)
  - Manning, D., 1885; cuid911 (Box 22, Folder 896B)
  - Mansfield, I.F., 1877; cuid912 (Box 22, Folder 897)
  - Marcon, John Belknap, 1883; cuid913 (Box 22, Folder 898)
  - Marcom, Jules (1824-1898), 1873; cuid914 (Box 22, Folder 899)
  - Marrhaly, ___________, 1899; cuid915 (Box 22, Folder 899A)
  - Marschall, August Friedrich.Grof von (1804-1887), 1877; cuid916 (Box 22, Folder 900)
  - Marshall, Brown, 1873; cuid917 (Box 22, Folder 901)
  - Martin, Handel T., 1889-1890 July; cuid918 (Box 22, Folder 902)
  - Martin, Handel T., 1890 August - 1893; cuid919 (Box 22, Folder 903)
  - Martin, Handel T., 1894-1895; cuid920 (Box 22, Folder 904)
  - Martin, Handel T., 1897-1899; cuid921 (Box 22, Folder 905)
  - Martin, John, 1883; cuid922 (Box 22, Folder 906)
  - Mason, Alfred Bishop (1851-1933), 1871-1883; cuid923 (Box 23, Folder 907)
  - Mason, Otis Tufton (1838-1908), 1890; cuid924 (Box 23, Folder 908)
  - Mason, S.C., 1882; cuid925 (Box 23, Folder 909)
  - Matthew, B.V., 1879; cuid926 (Box 23, Folder 910)
  - Maull and Fox, 1885-1898; cuid927 (Box 23, Folder 911)
  - Mayer, Alfred Marshall (1836-1897), 1884-1891; cuid928 (Box 23, Folder 912)
  - Mayer, Frank H. (1850-1954), 1884; cuid929 (Box 23, Folder 913)
  - Mayer, Mary M., 1898; cuid930 (Box 23, Folder 914)
  - Robert Mayer and Co., 1898; cuid931 (Box 23, Folder 915)
  - Mayer, William J., 1885; cuid932 (Box 23, Folder 916)
  - Maynard, H.J., 1880; cuid933 (Box 23, Folder 917)
  - Maynard, Mrs. J.S., 1870; cuid934 (Box 23, Folder 918)
  - Meek, Fielding Bradford (1817-1876), 1866-1867; cuid935 (Box 23, Folder 919)
  - Meek, Fielding Bradford (1817-1876), 1868-1876; cuid936 (Box 23, Folder 920)
  - Meigs, Montgomery Cunningham (1816-1892), 1882-1885; cuid937 (Box 23, Folder 921)
  - Meirs, John G., 1868-1870; cuid938 (Box 23, Folder 922)
  - Mendenhall, E., 1867; cuid939 (Box 23, Folder 923)
  - Mendenhall, Thomas Corwin (1841-1924), 1889-1893; cuid940 (Box 23, Folder 924)
  - Mercer, R.W., 1877-1878; cuid941 (Box 23, Folder 925)
  - Mersell, W.F., 1895; cuid942 (Box 23, Folder 926)
  - Merrill, George Perkins (1854-1929), 1898-1899; cuid943 (Box 23, Folder 927)
  - Merrill, Dr. J. King, 1880; cuid944 (Box 23, Folder 928)
  - Meyer, Otto, 1883-1885; cuid945 (Box 23, Folder 929)
  - Meyrat, Emile, 1879; cuid946 (Box 23, Folder 930)
  - Michelson, Albert Abraham (1852-1931), 1895; cuid947 (Box 23, Folder 931)
  - Miller, G.D.B., 1872; cuid948 (Box 23, Folder 932)
  - Miller, John F., 1872; cuid949 (Box 23, Folder 933)
  - Millet, J.B., 1880; cuid950 (Box 23, Folder 934)
  - Mills, Anson (1834-1924), 1874; cuid951 (Box 23, Folder 935)
  - Minor, Thomas T., 1872-1873; cuid952 (Box 23, Folder 936)
  - Minton, Maurice M., 1891; cuid953 (Box 23, Folder 937)
  - Mitchell, Charles L., 1886; cuid954 (Box 23, Folder 938)
  - Mitchell, Donald Grant (1822-1908), 1862-1889; cuid955 (Box 23, Folder 939)
  - Mitchell, John Kearsley (1859-1917), 1888; cuid956 (Box 23, Folder 940)